[
    {
        "question": "Which does not contribute significantly to the operational value of a large cloud provider like AWS?",
        "options" : [
            {
                "option" : "Multiregional presence"
            },
            {
                "option" : "Highly experienced teams of security engineers"
            },
            {
                "option" : "Deep experience in the retail sphere"
            },
            {
                "option" : "Metered, pay-per-use pricing"
            }
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following are signs of a highly available application? (Type TWO.)",
        "options" : [
            {
                "option" : "A failure in one geographic region will trigger an automatic failover to resources in a different region."
            },
            {
                "option" : "Applications are protected behind multiple layers of security."
            },
            {
                "option" : "Virtualized hypervisor-driven systems are deployed as mandated by company policy."
            },
            {
                "option" : "Spikes in user demand are met through automatically increasing resources."
            }
        ],
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer" : 1
            },
            {
                "answer" : 4
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How does the metered payment model make many benefits of cloud computing possible? (Type TWO.)",
        "options" : [
            {
                "option" : "Greater application security is now possible."
            },
            {
                "option" : "Experiments with multiple configuration options are now cost-effective."
            },
            {
                "option" : "Applications are now highly scalable."
            },
            {
                "option" : "Full-stack applications are possible without the need to invest in capital expenses."
            }
        ],
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer" : 2
            },
            {
                "answer" : 4
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following are direct benefits of server virtualization? (Type TWO.)",
        "options" : [
            {
                "option" : "Fast resource provisioning and launching"
            },
            {
                "option" : "Efficient (high-density) use of resources"
            },
            {
                "option" : "Greater application security"
            },
            {
                "option" : "Elastic application designs"
            }
        ],
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer" : 1
            },
            {
                "answer" : 2
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a hypervisor?",
        "answer": "Software used to administrate virtualized resources run on physical infrastructure"
    },
    {
        "question": "Describe server virtualization?",
        "answer": "Logically partitioning physical compute and storage devices into multiple smaller virtual devices"
    },
    {
        "question": "Describe Infrastructure as a Service products?",
        "answer": "Services that give you direct control over underlying compute and storage resources"
    },
    {
        "question": "Describe Platform as a Service products?",
        "answer": "Services that hide infrastructure complexity behind a simple interface"
    },
    {
        "question": "Describe Software as a Service products?",
        "answer": "Services that provide a service to end users through a public network"
    },
    {
        "question": "Describe scalability?",
        "answer": "The ability of an application to automatically add preconfigured compute resources to meet increasing demand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Describe elasticity?",
        "answer": "The ability of an application to increase or decrease compute resources to match changing demand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following characteristics most help AWS provide such scalable services? (Type TWO.)",
        "options" : [
            {
                "option" : "The enormous number of servers it operates"
            },
            {
                "option" : "The value of its capitalized assets"
            },
            {
                "option" : "Its geographic reach"
            },
            {
                "option" : "Its highly automated infrastructure administration systems"
            }
        ],
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer" : 1
            },
            {
                "answer" : 4
            }
        ]
    }
]    